(window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[]).push([["chunk-1beb9a02"],{"0454":function(t,e,s){"use strict";s.r(e);var i=function(){var t=this,e=t.$createElement,s=t._self._c||e;return s("div",{staticClass:"tests__content"},[s("div",{staticClass:"tests__header"},[s("h4",{staticClass:"tests__title"},[t._v("Список доступных тестов")]),s("div",{staticClass:"tests__filter"},[s("label",{staticClass:"label__filter",attrs:{for:"subjects"}},[t._v("Выберите предмет:")]),s("ul",{staticClass:"subjects__list"},[s("select",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:t.selected,expression:"selected"}],staticClass:"tests__filter-select",attrs:{id:"subjects",name:"subjects"},on:{change:function(e){var s=Array.prototype.filter.call(e.target.options,(function(t){return t.selected})).map((function(t){var e="_value"in t?t._value:t.value;return e}));t.selected=e.target.multiple?s:s[0]}}},[s("option",{attrs:{value:""}},[t._v("Все")]),s("option",{attrs:{value:"Математика"}},[t._v("Математика")]),s("option",{attrs:{value:"Логика"}},[t._v("Логика")]),s("option",{attrs:{value:"Қазақ тілі"}},[t._v("Қазақ тілі")])])])])]),s("ul",{staticClass:"tests__list"},[s("div",{staticClass:"tests__item names"},[s("div",{staticClass:"test__item-row"},[0==t.idx?s("div",{staticClass:"test__item-row names"}):t._e(),s("div",{staticClass:"tests__number"},[t._v("#")]),s("div",{staticClass:"tests__code"},[t._v("Код теста")]),s("div",{staticClass:"tests__subject"},[t._v("Предмет")]),s("div",{staticClass:"tests__class"},[t._v("Класс")]),s("div",{staticClass:"tests__class"},[t._v("Время (мин)")]),s("div",{staticClass:"tests__pass"},[t._v("Выбрать")])])]),t._l(t.tests,(function(e,i){return""==t.selected||t.selected==e.testsSubject?s("li",{key:e.id,staticClass:"tests__item"},[s("available-test-item",{attrs:{idx:i,test:e},on:{passTestAvailable:t.passTestAvailable}})],1):t._e()}))],2)])},n=[],a=(s("d3b7"),{components:{availableTestItem:function(){return s.e("chunk-89dfe3fa").then(s.bind(null,"9552"))}},beforeRouteLeave:function(t,e,s){this.available?s():s(!1)},mounted:function(){var t=document.createElement("script");t.setAttribute("src","https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/MathJax.js?config=TeX-AMS_HTML"),document.head.appendChild(t)},methods:{passTestAvailable:function(t){this.available=t.available}},data:function(){return{available:!0,selected:"",idx:0,tests:[{testsCode:"Логика-5-0003",testsSubject:"Логика",testsClass:"5",testsDuration:1,testsPoints:[{testQuestion:"Formula $a+b$ abc abc $c^d$",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"b"},{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"c"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"d"},{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"b"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"a"},{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"d"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"c"},{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"d"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"c"},{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"d"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"c"}]},{testsCode:"Математика-5-0004",testsSubject:"Математика",testsClass:"5",testsDuration:60,testsPoints:[{testQuestion:"Who is Terence Tao",testAnswers:["Mathematician","Writer","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"d"},{testQuestion:"Who is Albert Einstein",testAnswers:["Writer","Scienctist","Poet","Musician"],testAnswer:"c"}]}]}}}),r=a,c=(s("2f94"),s("2877")),o=Object(c["a"])(r,i,n,!1,null,null,null);e["default"]=o.exports},"2f94":function(t,e,s){"use strict";var i=s("7e52"),n=s.n(i);n.a},"7e52":function(t,e,s){}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=chunk-1beb9a02.d5954e49.js.map